exceedlms.com 2019-06-26

# Privacy Policy

Last Update: Mar 15, 2019

This Website Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy”) covers the web sites (“Web Sites”) operated by Intellum, Inc. (“Intellum” or “we” or “us” or “our”), including but not limited to Intellum.com, Exceedlms.com, Catcat.com, Facebookblueprint.com, Snacker.tv and Tribesocial.com. This Privacy Policy describes the types of information that we collect, what we do with it, how we protect it, and if and when we disclose it to third parties.  
This Privacy Policy is a part of and subject to the Intellum Terms of Service (“TOS”). Accordingly, when you enter into the TOS, you agree that you have read, understand, and agree that we can collect, use, and disclose your information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree or are not comfortable with any part of this Privacy Policy, you should not agree to the TOS (including this Privacy Policy) and you may not use the Web Sites.

Additional information about Intellum’s Data Privacy and Data Security practices, including Intellum’s commitments with regard to the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), can be found at the bottom of this page.

Information Gathering, Processing and Usage  
In connection with operation of the Web Sites and providing our services to you, we may collect the following types of user information (“Information”):

  * Personal Information. We collect personal information (“Personal Information”) from you and those individuals to whom you have given Web Site access. This Personal Information is used for billing purposes, account management purposes and for you to utilize the features of the Web Sites to which you have purchased access. Examples of Personal Information we might collect include but are not limited to: first name, last name, email address, mailing address, etc. We also collect Personal Information provided to us via any emails you send to us and via any user information added by you to the Web Sites (including Personal Information for users other than yourself).
  * Browsing Information. We collect information about your computer hardware and software and browsing activity.
  * Training Information. We collect information on learning/training activities within the Learning Management System (“LMS”)
  * Survey Information. We collect responses to any Intellum-sponsored Web Site surveys.

We collect and process this Information for the following general purposes: products and services provisioning, billing, identification and authentication, Web Site improvement, contacts, and research.

Intellum may disclose your Information to third parties under the following circumstances:

  * Disclosure to Successors. We may disclose your Information to any actual or potential successor-in-interest of ours, such as a company that is seeking to acquire us or the Web Site(s).
  * Third-Party Service Providers. We may use third-party partners to help us operate and maintain our Web Sites and deliver our products and services. We may also share your Information with our service providers and other third parties (“Affiliated Parties”) that provide products or services for or through the Web Sites or for our business (such as website or database hosting companies, CRMs, e-mail service providers, analytics companies, credit card processing companies and other similar service providers that use such information on our behalf or at the direction of your employer). Third-party service providers are contractually restricted from using or disclosing the Information, except as necessary to perform services on our behalf or to comply with legal requirements. Information may be processed in the European Union or the United States depending upon contractual requirements and in accordance with legal jurisdictions for the region(s) to which Intellum is subject.
  * Other Disclosure. We may disclose your Information to prevent an emergency, to protect or enforce our rights, to protect or enforce the rights of a third party, or as required or permitted by law (including, without limitation, to comply with a subpoena or court order).

Cookies  
To enhance your experience on our Web Sites, many of our web pages use "cookies". Cookies are bits of electronic information that a web site can transfer to a visitor’s hard drive to help tailor and keep records of his or her visit.  Cookies are required to use most Intellum services.  You may refuse to accept browser cookies by activating the appropriate setting on your browser. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access most of Intellum’s services. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you direct your browser to our Web Sites.  If you proceed with using our Web Sites without deactivating cookies through your browser, you are deemed to have accepted our use of cookies.

Web Beacons  
Pages of our services or our e-mails may contain small electronic files known as web beacons (also referred to as clear gifs, pixel tags and single-pixel gifs) that permit us, for example, to count users who have visited those pages or opened an e-mail and for other related website statistics (for example, recording the popularity of certain website content and verifying system and server integrity).

Data Storage  
Intellum uses third party vendors and hosting partners to provide some of the necessary hardware, software, networking, storage, and related technology required to run the Websites. Although Intellum owns the code, databases, and all rights to the Websites, you retain all rights to your data.

Protecting Personal Information  
We understand the importance of safeguarding your Information.  We employ administrative, physical, and electronic measures designed to protect your Information from unauthorized access.  We implement appropriate technical and organizational measures to ensure a level of security appropriate to the risk, taking into account technological reality, cost, the scope, context and purposes of processing weighted against the severity and likelihood that the processing could threaten individual rights and freedom.  Despite our efforts, we cannot guarantee the security of your Information. Accordingly, we assume no liability for any disclosure of data due to errors in transmission, unauthorized third-party access or other acts of third parties, or acts or omissions beyond our reasonable control.

Privacy Shield  
Intellum complies with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of Personal Information transferred from the European Union and the United Kingdom to the United States.  Intellum has certified to the Department of Commerce that it adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles.  If there is any conflict between the terms in this privacy policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern.  To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view our certification, please visit <https://www.privacyshield.gov/>

As such:

  * We participate in Privacy Shield.
  * We collect only Personal Information provided by the individual or the individual’s employer, including but not limited to name, address and email.
  * Intellum is subject to the Principles of all personal data received from the EU in reliance on the Privacy Shield.
  * Intellum collects Personal Information for authentication and personalization of the user experience.
  * Other than to the Third-Party Service Providers referenced above, Intellum does not disclose any Personal Information to third parties.
  * Intellum's customers can view their personal data in their profile in the application.
  * All user accounts are password protected, and an individual's Personal Information is only available to that individual when logged in.
  * Intellum is subject to the investigatory and enforcement powers of the FTC.
  * Intellum understands the possibility, under certain conditions, for the individual to invoke binding arbitration.
  * Intellum is required to disclose Personal Information in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements.
  * Intellum is liable in cases of onward transfers to third parties.

In compliance with the Privacy Shield Principles, Intellum commits to resolve complaints about our collection or use of your Personal Information.  EU individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding our Privacy Shield policy should first contact Intellum at:

Intellum has further committed to cooperate with EU data protection authorities (DPAs) with regard to unresolved Privacy Shield complaints concerning human resources data transferred from the EU in the context of the employment relationship. If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint from us, or if we have not addressed your complaint to your satisfaction, please contact the EU DPAs for more information or to file a complaint. The services of EU DPAs are provided at no cost to you.

Third Party Websites   
This Privacy Policy applies only to our Web Sites.  This Privacy Policy does not apply to any websites managed, maintained, and/or hosted by third parties not directly affiliated with Intellum that you may visit, e.g., via a link provided through the Web Sites or on a website maintained by any third party.  We do not control the privacy policies of other websites to which we may provide hyperlinks.  We cannot be responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such non-Intellum websites, and we do not control the practices of any of the third party websites or service providers to whose sites we link. We encourage you to learn more about the online privacy and data security policies of third party websites directly from such third parties, as their policies may differ from ours.

Children’s Privacy   
We are committed to protecting the privacy of children.  Our solutions are not intended for anyone under the age of 13. If you are under 13, do not use or provide any information on or through our solutions. If we learn we have collected or received Personal Data from a child under 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information. If you are a parent or guardian or otherwise believe we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us so that we can delete the child's information. Our services will never knowingly accept, collect, maintain or use any information from a child under the age of 13. If a child whom we know to be under the age of 13 sends Personal Data to us online, we will only use that information to respond directly to that child or notify parents.

Intellum Data Privacy & Data Security Statement  
This Data Privacy & Data Security Statement (the “Statement”), is provided by Intellum, Inc. (“Intellum”) to its Clients (each, a “Client”) and to users of Intellum’s Services affiliated with the Clients (“Users”). This Statement describes Intellum’s commitments with regard to data privacy and data security.   Intellum may update this Statement from time to time.  Updated versions will be published on Intellum’s website.

1\. Definitions

2\. Data Privacy

3\. Sub-Processors

4\. Data Subject Rights; Cooperation

5\. Return or Destruction of User Data

6\. Data Security

7\. Data Breach Procedures

8\. Cross-Border Transfers

Privacy Policy Updates  
This Privacy Policy may be updated periodically and without prior notice to reflect changes in our online information practices. We will post a prominent notice on this Web Site to notify you of any significant changes to our Privacy Policy and indicate at the bottom of the policy when it was most recently updated.

Questions  
Any questions about this Privacy Policy should be addressed to our Help Desk at [support@intellum.com](mailto:support@intellum.com?subject=Privacy%20Policy%20Questions).
